<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CalculatorApp</string>

    <string name="leftArrow">&#9664;</string>
    <string name="rightArrow">&#9654;</string>
    <string name="backSpace">&#9003;</string>

    <string name="welcomeText">"Welcome to Calculator!!!"</string>
    <string name="authorship"></string>

    <string name="versionStatement">Version 1.0, Oct 2019</string>

    <string name="user_guide_content"><b>Editing and Using User-Defined Functions</b>
        \n\n\n
        Functions are defined by first clicking <b>EDIT_F button</b>, which shows a dialog
        where users can pick one of six functions (f0 to f5) to edit. Clicking one of
        the functions will change the calculator to <b>edit mode</b> where text above the
        expression input will change to <b>Editing f$:</b> to remind the user they are in
        edit-mode. Entering edit mode will keep the previous mathematical expression
        unless it contains a user-defined function or ANS, as these cannot be used in
        user-defined functions Functions are inputted with the same scientific keyboard
        as before, but with four new buttons that appear in edit mode: x, y, z, and SAVE_F
        \n\n\n
        The function inputted can have between 0 and 3 variables. <b>x</b>, <b>y</b>, and <b>z</b> are the
        three variables that can be used in the functions. A function with 0 variables would
        be simply entering a mathematical expression as the function (e.g. <b>3</b> or <b>cos(45)</b> ),
        while a function with 3 variables would include <b>x</b>, <b>y</b>, and <b>z</b>. Functions are saved
        by clicking the SAVE_F button or the = button. The user will receive a message
        "Edited f$!" (where $ is replaced with 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5), which means that
        the function was successfully edited and saved. Edit-mode is automatically exited.
    \n\n\n
    Functions can be saved even if they are incorrect, but some processing takes place to
        ensure the functions behave as expected. Notably, if a single-variable equation
        was entered, the single-variable is always saved as <b>x</b> (even if only <b>y</b> or <b>z</b>
        was used). For a double-variable equation, this is always saved as
        using <b>x</b> and <b>y</b> (f(y,z) and f(x,z) would both be saved as f(x,y)). Variables
        are always shifted backwards towards the start of the alphabet (e.g. the <b>y</b>s in f(y,z)
        would become <b>x</b>s and the <b>z</b>s would become <b>y</b>s).
    \n\n\n
    Functions are called by pressing the USE_F button and clicking which function to use.
        Function arguments are separated using the comma button, and they always
        correspond to the variables in alphabetical order (e.g. f0(), f0(x), f0(x,y) or
        f0(x,y,z) if f0 was selected). Supplying the wrong number of function arguments
        will return an Input Error message. Note that multiple user-defined functions can be
        used in one mathematical expression, and an argument of a user-defined function can
        even be a user-defined function.
    \n\n\n
        For more information, the full user manual is available at:
        <a href="https://gitlab.cecs.anu.edu.au/u6999534/gp19s2/wikis/App-Summary-and-Manual">
            https://gitlab.cecs.anu.edu.au/u6999534/gp19s2/wikis/App-Summary-and-Manual</a></string>
</resources>
